[Music]
[音乐]
我将向您展示如何制作
I'm going to show you how to make an
基于的开放花机制
在1930年代的设计中，他们首先
I'm going to show you how to make an
opening flower mechanism that is based
出现在《每日快报》儿童
年度排名第三的是
opening flower mechanism that is based
on a design from the 1930s they first
叫花仙子，他有一些
底下相当复杂的折叠
on a design from the 1930s they first
appeared in the Daily Express children's
把花朵从页面上抬起来
我不知道他为什么这么做
appeared in the Daily Express children's
annual number three here it is it's
我认为可能是因为
使用的卡非常薄且脆弱
annual number three here it is it's
called the flower fairy he's got some
弯曲的，所以他想把它翻倍
给它力量来解除
called the flower fairy he's got some
quite complicated folding underneath
花了，我要去的版本
告诉你更简单一点
quite complicated folding underneath
that raises the flower up off the page
他们会表达孩子们的年度
第三，然后相同的设计
that raises the flower up off the page
and I can't quite work out why he did
或多或少在稍后重复
我相信这本书不是30多岁
and I can't quite work out why he did
that I think it might be because the
故事十，这是设计
那个时候，你可以看到那朵花是
that I think it might be because the
card is used is very thin and flimsy and
较小，它在页面上较低
相同的基本机制不同
card is used is very thin and flimsy and
bendy and so he wanted some of it double
艺术品，但基本机制相同
现在，我将向您展示如何做到这一点
bendy and so he wanted some of it double
to give it the strength to lift the
从一朵花开始，然后切一个粗糙的
广场，所以我只是偷工减料
to give it the strength to lift the
flower up and the version I'm going to
告诉你如何制作花
然后我会告诉你
flower up and the version I'm going to
show you is a little more simple so this
提出来，所以这就是我们
会瞄准这是花
show you is a little more simple so this
is they'll express children's annual
在非常基本的V形折叠上提出，这是
没有增加的直角v形折叠
is they'll express children's annual
number three and then the same design
在顶部创建一个沟壑，你
把面粉塞进你试过的
number three and then the same design
more or less was repeated later in the
遵循早期的设计
这些孔被切开，给它更多
more or less was repeated later in the
30s I believe in this book are no
精致但具有我所设计的
使它看起来不太正确，所以我
30s I believe in this book are no
stories number ten and here's the design
可能会略有不同
时间，但让我们为您
stories number ten and here's the design
that time and you can see the flower is
试一试，知道什么
你想真正做到，所以这是
that time and you can see the flower is
smaller it's lower on the page it's the
基本面粉将其对折，然后我们
需要这两个对角线，所以我就
smaller it's lower on the page it's the
same basic mechanism the different
用三角尺测量那些
将对齐中央的折痕
same basic mechanism the different
artwork but the same basic mechanism so
中央折痕处的投影机
那那个弹出窗口我现在要
artwork but the same basic mechanism so
now I'll show you how to make that I'll
得分都在45度
在这方面，我要去
now I'll show you how to make that I'll
start with a flower and just cut a rough
将它们延伸到整个花上
而这一点，这将给我们
start with a flower and just cut a rough
square so I'll just just cut the corners
这两个位的基本花形
挺身而出这两位
square so I'll just just cut the corners
off and show you how to make the flower
我们到了，然后按一下
只是为了确保它正常工作
off and show you how to make the flower
then I'll show you the mechanism that
那就是基本花
所以我有一个基础表，然后我
then I'll show you the mechanism that
that raises it up so this is what we
想要一些绿色的
代表花朵所以有一些
that raises it up so this is what we
will be aiming for this is the flower
绿色在这里，我将基地
现在我们需要基地之一
will be aiming for this is the flower
raised up on a very basic v-fold this is
种，因为他要坚持下去
这样它会向前折叠，
raised up on a very basic v-fold this is
a right-angle v-fold without increases
花贴在上面，所以我们就
像这样拿一张小卡片
a right-angle v-fold without increases
on the top that creates a gully that you
将它折成两半折得很好
这是一个直角V折，所以我们
on the top that creates a gully that you
stick the flour into you I tried
会在底部造成折痕
全部垂直成一厘米
stick the flour into you I tried
following the earlier design which has
再折一次，真的很好
切掉的角落也要折叠
following the earlier design which has
these holes cut in it that give it more
分开，所以我真的可以
加强那些
these holes cut in it that give it more
delicacy but with the design that I've
所以这些要贴在页面上
这样，现在我们想要额外的
delicacy but with the design that I've
made it doesn't look quite right so I
折痕增加了沟壑，所以我会做
这样的东西，大胆的
made it doesn't look quite right so I
might do it slightly differently this
好，这是一个计数器
折叠，所以我们将其推到现在
might do it slightly differently this
time but let's just scope for you to
当这卡住了，这将是
像那样
time but let's just scope for you to
play with it and work out you know what
这种机制的另一条路径
设计而不是机制是
play with it and work out you know what
you'd like to make really so this is the
后面的这点给你
多余的叶子粘在上面
you'd like to make really so this is the
basic flour fold it in half and then we
花，这是钝角v形，所以
当它折叠下来，这折叠下来
basic flour fold it in half and then we
need these two diagonals so I'll just
这样，当我们坚持
这到页面上这将
need these two diagonals so I'll just
use the set square to measure those that
像花一样粘在页面上
那，这将以这种方式折叠
use the set square to measure those that
would line up the central crease on the
但同时我们将拥有
他们后面的这两片叶子
would line up the central crease on the
projector with the central crease on
用另一种方式折叠下来，所以我们需要
将其定位在中间
projector with the central crease on
that and that pop-up now I'm going to
在那里，现在我们可以放花了
会陷入那个沟壑
that and that pop-up now I'm going to
score these they're both at 45 degrees
所以当我测试这个并尝试把
花开，你可以看到它的发展
score these they're both at 45 degrees
and on this side as well and I'm going
对基地来说太大了，所以我要
把它拉下来，因为它没有被卡住
and on this side as well and I'm going
to extend them right across the flower
真的很坚定，我要做
它比较短，所以我在那里剪了一块
and this one so this will give us the
并添加折痕并切掉该角
然后把那些折起来
and this one so this will give us the
basic flower shape these two bits will
这样会进入
它仍然不能正常工作，我必须
basic flower shape these two bits will
come forward and these two bits go back
让花变小现在我们坚持
花在那，但在我们坚持之前
come forward and these two bits go back
there we are and then I'll just press it
进入那个沟渠，让我们检查一下
它会坐在页面上我还不错
there we are and then I'll just press it
down just to make sure it's working and
可能会减少更多
所以我要花一点
down just to make sure it's working and
then that's the basic flower
较小的我也可以做一点
切割出更精致的裁片
then that's the basic flower
so I've got a base sheet and then I'm
这些角落只是为了给它一点
更多的花瓣缺陷，所以我现在就坚持
so I've got a base sheet and then I'm
going to want some green to make the the
进入我在那里创造的沟壑
完全实现了开放性
going to want some green to make the the
stand for the flowers so did have some
Jareau的花型设计引人注目
花掉了，我对这些不满意
stand for the flowers so did have some
green here I'll make the base there's
他们只是保持的角度
花比我想要的要近
green here I'll make the base there's
the base now we need one of these
看看这朵花
打开，如果你看这个花是
the base now we need one of these
species because he's going to stick on
更开放我要起飞
这个绿色的部分，我要用
species because he's going to stick on
like this it'll fold forward and the
我正在尝试的这件作品
昨天，如果您比较两个角度
like this it'll fold forward and the
flowers stick on the top so we'll just
折痕在这块上的角度和
比折角好得多
flowers stick on the top so we'll just
take a small piece of card like this
在这件作品上，我想也许这件作品
仍然有点高考虑
fold it in half crease it really well
你将不得不钝
角度V落在它后面，所以我要
this is a right angle V fold so we're
使这块小一点我
要去那里一块
this is a right angle V fold so we're
going to make a crease along the bottom
复述那些将是这样的
那
going to make a crease along the bottom
one centimeter up all at right angles
拿出那个角落
现在再试一次，我认为任何
one centimeter up all at right angles
again crease it really well cut out that
运气会更好
想要那样，我坚持一侧
again crease it really well cut out that
corner cut that off as well fold the
关闭它再次关闭它
看起来像一个更好的角度
corner cut that off as well fold the
pieces separately so I can really
中间的花
只是让那胶水稍微掉掉
pieces separately so I can really
reinforce those
过度，它把花粘在那里
正确，让我们尝试一下并关闭它
reinforce those
so these are going to stick on the page
确保一切正常似乎是
这次就像一朵更好的花，你
so these are going to stick on the page
like this and now we want the extra
认为我现在是专家，我把
留下一点点
like this and now we want the extra
creases that add to the gully so I'll do
较重的绿色，我不太满意
这就是它，所以我只需要大约一个
creases that add to the gully so I'll do
it up something like that and bold that
现在将一张纸的三分之一折成两半
大部分掉落在
it up something like that and bold that
well and this is a this is a counter
我们通常在折叠时使用的
底部的折痕使标签
well and this is a this is a counter
fold so we push that through and now
您使折痕形成向下
在这种情况下，我们想要的箭头
fold so we push that through and now
when this is stuck down this is going to
变成钝角v形，所以我们
将使折痕出现
when this is stuck down this is going to
be like that
当你朝着脊椎这样
打开它，你可以看到折痕
the other path of this mechanism rather
做一个向上的箭头，
他们会切成
the other path of this mechanism rather
the design rather than the mechanism is
我想要比这个小，但也许
叶片多一点，所以应该
the design rather than the mechanism is
this bit at the back this is giving you
能够站在花后面
这样的东西
this bit at the back this is giving you
the extra leaves that stick up above the
我会坚持一侧，然后另一侧
但通常是因为它们的花
the extra leaves that stick up above the
flower this is an obtuse angle v-fold so
有点复杂，所以我只是
尝试通过眼睛将其快速关闭
flower this is an obtuse angle v-fold so
as it folds down this this folds down
因此，如果棋子需要移动，他们可以
在胶水还软的情况下移动
as it folds down this this folds down
that way so when we come to sticking
不好，它仍然很软，我将其关闭
向下卡在角度上
that way so when we come to sticking
this on to the page this is going to
我已经到了这个钝角
v折他们显然是错误的
this on to the page this is going to
stick on the page with the flower like
所以我要把整个事情拖下去
虽然胶水仍然很粘，我要
stick on the page with the flower like
that and this is going to fold that way
改变角度并用
底座上的角度更小，因此您可以
that and this is going to fold that way
but at the same time we're going to have
使叶子更接近
花，现在把胶水涂在那些上，
but at the same time we're going to have
these two leaves behind it they're going
粘到位，我都将在
在同一时间，然后我们将其关闭
these two leaves behind it they're going
to fold down the other way so we need to
而胶水柔软，因此如果需要
他们仍然可以移动的四处移动
to fold down the other way so we need to
position this maybe around the middle
所以更像这样
我将其关闭以确保其正常工作
position this maybe around the middle
there and now we can put the flower is
是的，那很好，如果我
转过来，实际上你可以看到一点
there and now we can put the flower is
going to stick into that gully
我把它拉下来的黄色
页面，但这是整个角度
so when I test this and try putting the
事情停滞了，是的，我很高兴
接着就，随即
so when I test this and try putting the
flower into that you can see it's going
你知道它与
英雄版，但开篇不错
flower into that you can see it's going
to be too big for the base so I'm going
花
[音乐]
to be too big for the base so I'm going
to pull this off because it hasn't stuck
[掌声]
您
to pull this off because it hasn't stuck
really firmly yet and I'm going to make
[音乐]